qbox.io 2016-04-26

# Privacy Policy

Introducing Supergiant, a fundamental change in hosted Elasticsearch. Read more ▸

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) governs your access and use of the Qbox Services. By using the Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.  

You acknowledge and agree that Qbox collects, stores, and uses certain electronic information about you and your Account. 

## What We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about Users, including information by which you might be personally identified. We may collect this information directly from you when you provide it to us, and automatically as you navigate or use the Services. 

We also collect and use generalized, anonymous information about all Users. This information cannot be used to identify or isolate your personal information. 

## How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We use or disclose your information solely for the purpose of providing the Qbox Services to you through the operation of the Qbox business or for legal purposes, all according to the following principles: 

  * _As you direct or consent_ : We may share or use your information when you direct us or consent to us sharing or using your information.
  * _For legal purposes_ : We may share or use your information (a) to comply with applicable laws, regulations, court orders, legal processes, or to respond to any government or regulatory request, (b) to detect or otherwise manage fraud, security, or technical issues, (c) to protect the safety, rights, or property of any person, the public, or Qbox, or (d) to enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including the Terms of Use and for billing and collection.
  * _For external processing_ : We may share your information with third parties who are necessary for us to provide the Qbox Services and process information on our behalf (for example: to process payments or to ensure compliance with appropriate security and confidentiality measures on our behalf). 
  * _To contact you about goods and services_ : We may use your information to contact you about Services that may be of interest to you, and to enable us to display or direct communications to you; and
  * _For business purposes_ : We may disclose your information (a) to our current or future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, and other companies under common control and ownership, or (b) to a buyer or other successor in connection with, or during negotiations, a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Qbox’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding.

We may use generalized, anonymous information for any purpose and disclose it to third parties in our sole discretion. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to learn how your “personal information” (as defined in the Shine the Light Law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) is shared with third-parties, what categories of personal information we have shared with third-parties in the preceding year, as well as the names and addresses of those third-parties, please e-mail us at: [support@qbox.io](mailto:mailto:support@qbox.io); or send us mail to: 

Qbox  
1722 N. College Ave, Suite C-209  
Fayettevile, AR 72703 

Further, if you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: [support@qbox.io](mailto:mailto:support@qbox.io); or send us mail to: 

Qbox  
1722 N. College Ave, Suite C-209  
Fayettevile, AR 72703 

Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law. 

## Security of Information

Qbox has taken reasonable steps to safeguard User information. However, Qbox cannot guarantee the security of your information. By using the Services, you agree that you provide your personal information and content at your own risk. You are solely responsible for maintaining the security of your Account. 

## Miscellaneous

Qbox uses or may use third-party providers for various aspects of the Services, including the processing of payments and fees. By using the Services, you acknowledge and agree that you will also be subject to the third-party terms and conditions associated with those third-party services. Those terms and conditions may be materially different than our policies, especially with regard to information privacy and security. You acknowledge and understand that the third-party terms and conditions will apply to your Account and information, including, but not limited to, financial information collected to enable and process payments on the Services. 

Qbox may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in its discretion. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting the revised policy. Revised policies will be posted at this page, so we encourage you to review it regularly. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the posted date for this policy and, in some cases and in our sole discretion, we may provide you with additional notice (for example: by notice on our homepage or sending you a notification). 

By using the Services, you agree that Qbox will not be responsible or liable to you or any third party for any consequence, loss, or damage arising (directly or indirectly) from or relating to any of the circumstances described in this Privacy Policy.
